District 4 and 5, keep up your bombardment!
Roger!
I frequent that super market
shooting beams right now...
This just shows you Ratatoskr's facilities
extend well beyond the underground.
All ships! Commence fire
on the enemy battleships!
Wizard Team, support our Spirits!
Roger!
Gabriel!
Haniel!
Kaleidoscope!
So this is Gabriel?
I do feel like it's grown stronger.
Yes!
Now to just scatter our foes!
So thrilling, so thrilling!
To think they would try
to stop me with such forces!
They sure are underestimating me.
Hmph, here come the mass-produced models.
Mass-produced models?
You're the one person
I don't want to hear that from.
I've thought this for a while,
but your character overlaps
with ours, doesn't it?
Bring it on.
I'll lay out your heads
before your beloved "Father".
What is this?
Captain, this is what Origami
was trying to tell us about, isn't it?
Looks like it.
This isn't a fight against Spirits anymore.
Hello, captain of the JGSDF's AST.
This is Irene Fox from DEM's
Second Executive Branch.
DEM?
Cutting to the point,
please follow our orders
and charge the Spirits.
We'll provide cover.
Huh? What's the big idea?
You all are at least capable of that, right?
Later.
Captain, are we going to follow DEM's orders?
If there's a Spirit before us,
it's our job to defeat them,
regardless of DEM's orders.
Let's go!
Be careful of that chill!
It'll freeze you and your Territory!
Roger!
Wha?!
Michael, Lataib!
Huh?
Hmm, are you all the AST
that Origami mentioned?
Y-You're a Spirit, right?
You saved us?
They were intending to use you all as decoys.
Don't fall for it.
We heard about you from Origami,
so please get away from here.
C-Captain, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Thanks to that woman.
All of you!
Start preparing to look for another job!
Artemisia.
Long time, no see.
It's Origami Tobiichi, right?
Seeing you gives me the creeps.
Have we met somewhere before?
You've had your memories manipulated by DEM.
Huh?
It's possible for us to cure you of that.
Are you suggesting
that Westcott is deceiving me?
Yes.
Sorry, but I can't believe you.
After all, you're Spirits.
Whoa, I'm the one you'll be facing!
Yoshinon!
Here I go!
Bad girls get frozen!
Metatron!
You're quite good.
Oririn!
This a little bad news,
but Ellen is heading your way!
You came, Ellen?
Wise judgment.
You've matured.
Karen.
Please handle the rest.
Elliot.
May I tell a joke to help
calm tensions in the room?
Oh?
Let's run, Elliot.
Leave behind Ratatoskr,
the Spirits, everything.
We can go live somewhere
together, just the two of us.
I would like at least three kids.
Karen.
That was my best joke.
Yeah, you have talent as comedian.
Origami Tobiichi and Mana Takamiya...
Perfect. I'll eliminate you both together.
Who goes there?!
Hey. Long time, no see, Ellen.
Did you have fun acting like you're
the strongest in a world without me?
Elliot!
This is lame.
Right? I can't believe we're being assigned
the boring work of assaulting cannons.
Oh, look, look.
Looks like this might get a little interesting.
Beelzebub Yeled!
So weak!
I wanted to play a bit more, but Father
will get mad if we take too long.
You're finished!
Leave this place to us!
Evacuate. Please fall back.
Th-Thanks...
Are you serious?
Princess and Berserk!
The fighters are all here!
Do you think you can beat us with numbers?
With me, one is all, and all are one.
No matter how many of us you kill,
we won't die as long as Beelzebub exists.
How do you hope to kill a woman who can't die?
Sorry, Nibeelcole, but we're not your opponent.
We have someone much better
suited to facing you!
Affirmative. We're simply their backup.
Huh?
Shido Itsuka?
Wow, that's awfully bold, isn't it?
You are our opponent?
Are you underestimating us?
If I kill you, then it means
my father has won this battle.
Are you stupid?
Now I'll have a great present for Father!
Nibeelcole, I love you.
Huh?
What's going on?!
Nibeelcole eliminated! It worked!
Nibeelcole is still a Spirit, too.
Which means Shido's power can seal her, as well.
Nibeelcole originates from Beelzebub,
but he didn't manage to steal
the entirety of Nia's crystal.
Meaning I'm still influencing Little Rouge.
So whether or not he can seal them
depends on my affection for him.
Yes. This is a vulgar way of putting it,
but they're loose girls whose bodies are
honest no matter how much they say no.
Raphael!
Now, let's begin, Nibeelcole.
It's time for our date.
Don't underestimate us!
Then I just need to avoid getting close!
Now, who's next?
Father!
I'm not letting you go, kittens.
The impact's more impressive than I imagined.
Way to go, Shido!
I think this what they call unparalleled.
Watchful. There seems to be
no need for us to act.
That's not the case. Here they come!
We won't let you interfere!
Shido, we leave the rest to you.
You can count on me!
Come on, come on.
Give up already. It's no use running.
Shido! Behind you!
You're impressive.
So are you.
But you can't win just by running.
I wonder what you're thinking?
Perfect timing.
This is Artemisia Ashcroft with DEM's
Second Executive Branch.
I'm currently engaged with a Spirit.
Lend assistance.
Sorry, but we can't meet your expectations.
After all, we're unemployed!
A draw?
No, it's my win.
No.
It's our win.
Huh?
Michael, Lataib.
Was I useful to you, Origami?
Thank you.
Ultimately our two-stage decoy strategy worked.
Though I honestly intended
to ask Mana to handle it.
I'm sorry I was delayed!
It took time for me to handle the Bandersnatch!
Don't worry.
You made the right decision, Captain.
Don't give me that shit!
Jeez, there's no going back for us now!
Good bye to my life as a public servant.
You're the real one, not a clone, right?
Yes, I'm surprised you could tell.
Kurumi, I...
This is the battlefield.
You mustn't let your guard down.
Y-Yeah. Thank you.
You saved my life.
You're making an awfully big deal about it.
I'm not just referring to now.
I'm honestly grateful for
all the times you've saved me so far.
I really wanted to tell you that in person.
My, my, why thank you.
Then might I have your Spirit power
as a show of appreciation?
That's a different matter!
That's unfortunate.
Then I'll have to change my approach.
Kurumi, I am grateful to you!
But you know,
I don't recall ever asking you to fight
in my stead while I hide from DEM!
I would never be happy if you saved me
in exchange for your own life!
You underestimate me, don't you?
You just need to remain quietly on the ship.
Then once the battle is over,
you can greet me with tears of gratitude,
and offer your Spirit power up to me!
That just means I would
die to you instead of DEM!
I already told you, didn't I?
I'll use your Spirit power to go to the past
and defeat the Spirit of Origin!
When you next come to, you'll be in
a new world full of peace and happiness!
You think it'll go that well?
I don't want to hear that from the man
who actually managed to alter the past!
Now that you mention it, I did do that, damn it.
Once I alter the past,
the existence of Spirits
and your death will be no more!
What are you unsatisfied with about that?
Then the very fact that you and I met
would also be no more, now wouldn't it?!
I love you!
And I know you love me, too!
Wh-What are you saying?!
Don't forget!
I've experienced your memories with Yod!
I know how you feel!
Even if that is true,
saying that while you're kissing
another woman is deplorable.
I'm truly sorry about that!
Kurumi, listen to me.
Once this battle is over,
I'll return to the past!
Huh?
I won't redo everything, only the bad parts!
I'll seal the Spirit of Origin's power,
and use that power to rewrite history!
I'll make it so the misfortune
that befell your friend, you,
and all of the other Spirits never happened,
and I'll ensure that I meet you
and everyone else once again!
I'll recreate the ultimate
favorable and happy history!
What are you...? Do you have any chance to...?
You said it yourself, right?
I'm the only the person in this world
who has successfully rewritten history!
Stop ignoring me
and creating your own little world!
Die!
Kurumi, dodge!
Dalet.
Me!
See? I proved useful, didn't I?
Yes.
I hate to admit it,
you proved worth keeping alive.
Please...
Be honest with our own feelings.
Kurumi.
That clone was cocky, rebellious,
meddlesome, and hopeless...
but she finally proved useful before dying.
Shido, do you remember our competition?
Competition?
Whoever makes the other fall for them wins?
Let's continue our chat
after this battle is over.
Once we've driven away DEM...
I wouldn't mind offering you my lips.
You mean it, Kurumi?!
That's only if we can defeat DEM.
Can you do that, Shido?
Of course I can!
If I can't pull that off,
then how could I face the Spirit of Origin?!
Huh?
What?!
Episode 3
The Spirit's Resurrection
Episode 4 "The Spirit of Origin"
That is a memory of a distant past,
and the tale of how Mio and Shinji met.
Next Episode is Episode 4:
The Spirit of Origin.
I'll never let go of you again.